Guide to the Mary Dowdell Ashley Film Collection, 1937-1975 RL.10048
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Mary Dowdell Ashley film collection
1937-1975
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Ashley, Mary Dowdell
RL.10048
3 Linear Feet 13 16mm film reels
The collection consists of approximately 9,000 film feet (about 5.5 hours across 13 reels) of 16mm home movies, shot from the 1930s to the 1970s by Mary Dowdell Ashley. The footage consists primarily of Ashley's family and community life in Montgomery, Alabama and the Gulf Coast area.
Biographical note
Mary Barnett Dowdell was born in Montgomery, Alabama, in 1917, to Annie Solomon Dowdell and William Shapard "Shap" Dowdell. In 1919 the family moved to Pelham Manor, New York, where Shap Dowdell managed the New York office of the Montgomery firm Weil Brothers Cotton. Shap died unexpectedly in late 1937, and in 1938 the family returned to Montgomery. In 1941 Mary Dowdell married John Myrick Ashley, an independent insurance agent, in Montgomery. They had five children, Virginia, Ann, Bonnie, Rick, and Shap.
On her 16th birthday, Mary Dowdell received a 16mm camera, and over the next 40 years recorded with it a very active life, which included managing a large household in Montgomery as well as a country property in Coosa County, maintaining membership in a variety of community organizations, and travelling. She died in 1983.
Provenance
The Mary Dowdell Ashley films were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift between 2010, 2011, and 2013.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by original reel number.
Collection Overview
The collection consists of approximately 9,000 film feet (about 5.5 hours across 13 reels) of 16mm home movies, shot from the 1930s to the 1970s by Mary Dowdell Ashley. The footage consists primarily of Ashley's family and community life in Montgomery, Alabama and the Gulf Coast area. Additionally, there is some documentation of African American life in the South in the mid-century: footage on Reel 6 shows an outdoor African American baptism in Shorter, Alabama, in 1939, as well as street scenes in Montgomery from that same year; footage on Reel 7 captures the circa 1950 Thanksgiving Day parade leading up to the Alabama State versus Tuskegee football game, an annual rivalry between the two historically black institutions; and there is footage on Reel 11 of cotton picking. Some commercial footage is mixed in with the longer compilation reels.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Use of these materials may require production of listening or viewing copies. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.
The collection may contain materials to which the Acknowledgment of Legal Responsibilities and Privacy Rights form applies. Patrons must sign this form before using the collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Montgomery (Ala.); Film; Audiovisual materials; 16mm; Home movies
- Films, 1936-1967; 1
  Scope and Contents
  Most of the films have a two-part description. The first part is comprised of the notes on the original film cans, created by Mary Dowdell Ashley. The children of Mary Dowdell Ashley created additional descriptions of the films, which are provided here verbatim. The first six reels are compilation reels containing multiple rolls of film spliced together, and the descriptions for these are subdivided into sequence (roll) number and scene number.
  - Reel 1, compilation, segments 1-12, 1952-1955; 1
    Reel 1. Sequence 1. Scene 1. Montgomery, AL, downtown: Dale's Penthouse outside restaurant on balcony (family went there after Myrick's christening): view of downtown Montgomery -capitol building, red tile dome of 1st Baptist Church; Bonnie (blue dress) with Ann (also blue dress) behind her; Joy Clark in yellow skirt; Daddy holding Myrick; Louise Clark in yellow skirt. Standing against railing: Louise, Joy, Ann, Bonnie, Ginny, Daddy holding Myrick. Panorama view of downtown.
    Reel 1. Sequence 1. Scene 2. Hull Street, front yard: Easter egg hunt. Louise Clark? (red dress); Bonnie (red hair) & Ann (both in blue dresses); multiple children; Laura Hutchinson? (blue coat with white stripes at collar; beside her in blue: Inge Hill; Bonnie again; Georgina Terry in light blue coat and next to her in white, Edith Johnston?; Laura Hutchinson again with brother Hank (in gray).
    Reel 1. Sequence 1. Scene 3. Hull Street, back yard: Daddy with Bonnie (green coat & hat), Ann (red coat & hat), & Ginny (plaid coat).
    Reel 1. Sequence 1. Scene 4. Location? -- Graham Haven: Mother's friends -- Libby Foster? (in blue), ? (red/white plaid, several friends standing or sitting by table, Mother (in white) at back, Katie Seawell sitting with legs propped on table, Frances Hill (in glasses) sitting. View of water -- ? at end of pier; Eloise Virgin (red/gray/black top) walked onto pier. 4 women on pier: ?, Libby (blue dress) standing, Frances Nicrosi ? (pinkish shirt & vest) sitting, Frances Lamb (in suit) standing, Mother (hat, light blue shirt, jeans) standing, Libby on chair & Frances Lamb & ? & Eloise Virgin.
    Reel 1. Sequence 1. Scene 5. Hull Street, sidewalk in front: Bonnie (horizontal striped shirt); Big Ann, holding Myrick; Ginny (in dress); Ann (white shirt & blue shorts), Dear. Myrick crawling & dragging left leg on sidewalk; Dear (white scarf) - dark.
    Reel 1. Sequence 1. Scene 6. Hull Street, back yard: Myrick, barefooted & sitting on grandfather (Shap Dowdell)'s chair; tried to walk.
    Reel 1. Sequence 2. Scene 1. Montgomery, AL -- Helen Cottingham's kindergarten, Ann & Bonnie's birthday (March 1953): sand - Ann (in blue); Ann holding rope & jumping rope; Bonnie (in blue) swinging (can see 1949 green Plymouth (family car) in background). Ann jumping rope with each end held by friends. ? (in red), Charlotte Poyntz holding ukelele; behind Ann, Edith Johnston (blue dress & slip showing) & 2 others. Then see at left ? (in white sweater), ? (in green dress), next to ? (in red); Charlotte Poyntz ? on bike, Lila Ashley, Ann (in blue); then ? & then Edith Johnston; Miss Cottingham may be behind, between Ann & ?. Other side of Charlotte: male & then Bonnie.
    Reel 1. Sequence 2. Scene 2. Hull Street, front yard: Daddy holding Myrick's hand & Ann holding beach ball; then Ann, Myrick, Bonnie. Good view of house with Daddy, Myrick, Ann in front. Same scene, another time: probably Easter Sunday, dressed for Sunday School: Ginny, Ann, & Bonnie (all in hats).
    Reel 1. Sequence 2. Scene 3. Oak Park (Montgomery city park): Myrick (sailor suit) on Merry Go-Round; roller coaster; Bessie Seawright holding Shap. Car ride. Airplane ride: Bonnie in airplane with ? behind her. Ann (same dress as Bonnie -- blue & white with applique of red & white strawberries). Bessie holding Shap. Ferris wheel: Ann & Ginny probably next to her. Bonnie on Merry-Go-Round. Dark.
    Reel 1. Sequence 2. Scene 4. Hull Street, back yard: Myrick on sliding board.
    Reel 1. Sequence 3. Scene 1. Mary Esther, FL: back of Bonnie, Ginny (dark suit), & Mary Ellis Carrere (light suit) climbing into boat; Daddy at back by motor in adjacent boat. Ann & male climbing in. Other boat again -- Daddy at back, Bonnie & Ginny. Mary Ellis & Ginny diving off end of pier. Bonnie, Daddy. Little Ann on far left and male between her & ?. 2 children & 3 adults (1 female & 2 males) in boat. Back to boat with Daddy by motor & Bonnie at other end. Bonnie onto pier with Little Ann & ?. View of Santa Rosa Sound. East Pass Bridge or another bridge in Destin area. ? catching fish. Back to Santa Rosa Sound near pier.
    Reel 1. Sequence 3. Scene 2. Mary Esther, FL (cont'd): in water (sound): Mother with Shap in inner tube -- Bonnie (in halter & shorts) standing. Ginny & Mary Ellis wrapped in sheets & towels; Ann (in blue plaid shirt) wading. Dark. View of shore from boat -- pier with 2 houses in background. Bonnie & Ann (in life jackets) at bow of boat; middle of boat: Myrick (in red life jacket); Ginny & Mary Ellis (no life jackets). Close-ups of those on boat including Daddy. Bonnie & Ann in shallow water: both swim.
    Reel 1. Sequence 3. Scene 3. Mary Esther, FL: Gulf side of Santa Rosa Island: back of Bonnie in inner tube on sand; Ann building drip sand castle; Mary Ellis & Ginny standing in water, & then both swim. Daddy & Myrick on sand. Mother in 2 piece bathing suit.
    Reel 1. Sequence 4. Scene 1. Montgomery, AL: "Rose Mary," Inge Hill's home: Pony riding: Bonnie holding reins with Myrick in front of Ann on pony. Daddy leads pony around. View of house. Inge, jr. In tree with boy on ground. Daddy in bow tie with Myrick with boy behind him on pony. Frances Hill near head of pony & Ann next to her, then Bonnie (white shirt & dark pants) & Inge, jr. beside her.
    Reel 1. Sequence 4. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue, driveway & side yard: Myrick & Meri Wood. Myrick walks towards 3 girls in driveway. Back yard: little girl ? on swing. Myrick (cowboy hat & boots) at top of sliding board & slides down. Shap in taylor tot. View of back yard. Myrick, holding croquet stick, beside Shap in taylor tot. Bonnie (in dress) bats a croquet ball. Shap standing & holding stick & ball. Swing set: Bonnie is closest & Gray Thames on other side of double swing -- Myrick tries to stop them with croquet stick. Shap crawling. Shap on swing. Ginny (blue shorts). Myrick & perhaps Shot Thames leaning on swingframe. Gray on swing & Bonnie next to her. Shap on ground crying. Another view of swingframe with same people. Good view of back of house: clothes on clothesline drying on upstairs back porch.
    Reel 1. Sequence 4. Scene 3. Mary Esther, FL: Shap in water with hands on boat; Meri Wood beside him. Bonnie in life jacket. Daddy on right of boat & on other side: Bonnie, Meri, Shap. Myrick in life jacket in water & Meri at edge of water with her back to the camera. Exie Lee Walker holding Shap?
    Reel 1. Sequence 5. Scene 1. Mary Esther, FL: Aunt Mamie & Uncle Phil's house. In water: Ann (tallest), Bonnie (pony tails) & Myrick. Ann & Bonnie swimming & Myrick in large inner tube. Close-up of Bonnie, Ann, Myrick. Daddy in chair smoking.
    Reel 1. Sequence 5. Scene 2. Mary Esther, FL: Gulf side of Santa Rosa Island: Bonnie & Ann in water. Bonnie swimming. Daddy in water. Myrick digging in sand. Mother in 2 piece bathing suit in water.
    Reel 1. Sequence 5. Scene 3. Wolf River, MS, near Pass Christian & Gulfport: pier -- Little Ann in reddish bathing suit with white trim holding Shap; swims across river holding Shap in inner tube. Myrick on pier holding inner tube. Views of river. Shap crying while walking towards camera. Little Ann in shorts. Ann (dark suit) & girl? in blue or green suit near hammock. Mollie in white underpants & 2 others? Little Ann in hammock holding Mollie, Bonnie standing. Shap at bottom of steps & then beside hammock.View of Stauss Haus with hammock in front.
    Reel 1. Sequence 6. Scene 1. Bankhead Avenue, back yard. Birthday party for Ann & Bonnie (March 1955): pony rides. ? In pigtails on pony. Exie in green uniform near pony. Lots of children. Dirt piles in vacant lot next door. Driveway scene: one walking on stilts, others playing, etc., & some roasting marshmellows. Bonnie (in white shirt) on pony. Children on swings, etc. Children playing on dirt piles next door.
    Reel 1. Sequence 6. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue, back yard: another day. Birthday of ?, maybe Meri Wood. Meri Wood (in white dress) & Bonnie on right. Little girl? beside small table. Shap in sailor suit. Myrick in sailor suit on rocking horse. Meri opening present.
    Reel 1. Sequence 6. Scene 3. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Close-up of Bonnie, with Ginny in background. Myrick sucking thumb. Ginny with Ann into background. Front walk: Myrick at left, then Lila Ashley, Bonnie, Ann with Ginny behind.
    Reel 1. Sequence 7. Scene 1. Montgomery Country Club: arbor-like area behind the old Country Club main building. Old big & baby pools. Daddy & Shap walking into baby pool. Lots of messy tables, probably from a party the night before. Ann (left) & Bonnie (right) diving into big pool.
    Reel 1. Sequence 7. Scene 2. Perdido, AL: Billy Thetford on boat. ? diving off board at end of pier. Few people & then Bonnie at end of diving board from which she dives. Ginny (red suit). Close-up of Myrick holding onto life jacket & Randolph Candler doing the same. Close-up of a Thetford (?), who ducks under water.
    Reel 1. Sequence 7. Scene 3. "Huntingdon" Kowliga, near Wetumka, AL:. Large set of swings. Friends of Mother & Daddy sitting. Close-up of a baby with pacifier in mouth. Close-up of Mildred Duncan (white collar).
    Reel 1. Sequence 7. Scene 4. location?: Big Ann (white hat) & ??. Bruce & Dorothy Thomas from San Antonio. Virginia Thomas on right of 2 sisters (Emily & Dorothy).
    Reel 1. Sequence 7. Scene 5. Mary Esther, FL (?): rubber raft with Shap in front of Myrick. View of house our family rented. Children in water - hard to identify. Bonnie (navy suit with white trim) in an inner tube. Close-up of little girl? in inner tube.
    Reel 1. Sequence 8. Scene 1. AEA holidays (Alabama Educational Association): Family trip to Florida via Georgia. Okefenokee Swamp (GA): otters, alligators. Ginny (white sweater & designed skirt) walking with Myrick. Ann in pinkish peddle pushers.Myrick with ducks. Ginny with Ann & Bonnie (latter 2 dressed alike) & Myrick.
    Reel 1. Sequence 8. Scene 2. AEA cont'd: Marineland, FL: dolphin feeding; underwater scene. Flippy the "educated" porpoise. Bonnie, Ginny, Ann, Mother, Myrick: standing with ocean in background. More underwater scenes.
    Reel 1. Sequence 9. Scene 1. AEA cont'd: St. Augustine, FL: Castle of San Marcos -- Ginny (light blue skirt), Daddy, then standing next to each other. Myrick & Ann. Fountain. Far left: Ann, then Bonnie, & Ginny & Myrick to right.
    Reel 1. Sequence 9. Scene 2. AEA cont'd: Cross Sewanee River on way to Wakulla Springs. DARK -- underwater. Views from glass-bottomed boat. Off boat: Mother, Myrick, Ginny, Ann, Bonnie.
    Reel 1. Sequence 9. Scene 3. Bankhead Avenue: Shap in snowsuit & red hat, barefooted. Myrick in red cowboy shirt. Another day: Myrick in Sunday clothes & coonskin cap. Ginny (green dress); Margaret Harris (pink dress); Bonnie (white). Good view of Bankhead house.
    Reel 1. Sequence 10. Scene 1. Mayland, TN: Camp Nakanawa: waterfront; some cabins; waterfront again. Daddy standing beside rowboats. Horse ring by fence: Minnie Lee Richardson, Ginny, Ginny Hubbard. Round house. Tennis courts. Waterfront: canoe contest; swim meet.
    Reel 1. Sequence 10. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue: Shap & Myrick in sailor suits. Close-up of Shap & then Mollie. Ann & Bonnie in back of Myrick & Shap & Mother. Station wagon (fake wood trim) & green Plymouth. Between cars: Gray Thames, Bonnie & Ann behind Myrick & Shap & then Exie.
    Reel 1. Sequence 11. Scene 1. Mary Esther, FL: on boat in life jackets: Myrick, Shap, Ann with Bonnie behind. View from boat: houses along Santa Rosa Sound. Boat again. Another boat with Daddy on bow. Bubba Branson? driving boat. Mother or Ginny skiing. Male skiing.
    Reel 1. Sequence 11. Scene 2. Mary Esther, FL:, sound side of Santa Rosa Island: Myrick, Ann, Bonnie in life jackets. Pier on sound side: Daddy, Myrick, Bonnie, Ann. Scallops underwater near pier; close-ups of scallops out of water.
    Reel 1. Sequence 11. Scene 3. Mary Esther, FL: Gulf side of Santa Rosa Island: sea oats, sand, water. Jeep with Daddy lifting Shap out & Myrick climbing out. Sunset over Gulf.
    Reel 1. Sequence 11. Scene 4. Mary Esther, FL: sound side of Santa Rosa Island: Daddy & Ann, Bonnie, Myrick in water.
    Reel 1. Sequence 12. Scene 1. Bankhead Avenue: Ginny on stilts & Uncle Eddie in background. Close-up of Mollie. Foreground: Bonnie, Mollie, & Shap in toy fire engine. Backyard: Bonnie standing at top of sliding board; back of Ann on left. Driveway & carport: Ginny (white top) & Margaret Harris (plaid top) on stilts. To left: Uncle Eddie putting Mollie on swing. Myrick on adjacent swing. Uncle Eddie pushing Mollie -- Myrick on left & Ann on right. Little Ann holding unhappy Shap. Shap walking & crying.
    Reel 1. Sequence 12. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Bonnie holding doll, Ginny (red flower corsage). Daddy holding Shap, Myrick, Ann holding doll. Laundry basket full of presents. Mother in fur coat holding Shap; Myrick, Ann, Bonnie, Ginny (Daddy must be taking movie). DARK. Another day: Susan Candler (blond hair) ? Ann, Myrick, Randolph Candler. Bonnie using knife on wooden box. Gray Thames, then Bonnie holding cat. Dirt piles next door: Ann, Bonnie, Susan Candler, Gray Thames, Randolph Candler, Myrick. Green Plymouth in background.
    - Original 16mm film, 1952-1955; 1300 film feet (Box 1, Film-reel RL10048-F16-0001)
  - Reel 2, compilation, segments 13-24, 1956-1958; 2
    Original notes on can: 13: Bankhead - Rick and Shap in cowboy suits - Spring 1956 - Mississippi River - New Orleans - Zoo, 3rd grade, Mrs. Haber, Ann; 14: Spring 1956 - Hull St. Big Ann - Stausses - Ann D. (baby) Bonnie and Gray - Bonnie, camp, Mary Esther 1956 - Mary Ellis and Dolphin. Gulf - all 5 children; 15: 1956 - Mary Esther - Mary Wood and Mary Ellis. Uncle Phil's boat. Perdido diving. Coosa. Country Club; 16: 1955 - Bankhead - Tutsie's puppies - Shap and Mollie - Backyard on slide. Mother, Dad, Little Ann and Eddie. (Lots of blank) Coosa, falls; 17: Summer 1957 - Jamestown and Williamsburg. Boat trip - Ann, Bonnie, Rick (sleeping) Shap and Dad; 18: Summer 1957 - Ocracoke - Bird Island - Marshall and Exie; 19: Summer 1957 - Perdido, Garth pier. Lake Martin, Hubbard and Ellie; 20: 1957 - Von Gal pool. Perdido. Garth skiis - Rusty Seawell; 21: January 1958 - Coosa - Rick's Birthday party - Billy, Thomas, Joesph, Julian. Easter; 22: 1958 - Mary Esther - Deep sea fishing. Swim meet. East "Y". Hula contest - Murchinson; 23: Floyd School chearleading. Bankhead w/puppies. Backyard - Ann and Roselyn Weil - Coosa party for Bonnie - Jack's Creek; 24: Blue and Gray Tennis. Rick the Cowboy. Swim meet. Mary Esther. Exie.
    Additional description:
    Reel 2. Sequence 13. Scene 1. Bankhead Avenue, driveway: Mollie joined by Uncle Eddie; Myrick & Shap in cowboy outfits with Tootsie in the background; Daddy, Little Ann, & children: Emily Marks (?) on left & Mollie beside Daddy; Uncle Eddie between Daddy & Mollie; Bonnie walks towards Daddy; Mollie walks towards Uncle Eddie & Bonnie; Myrick & Shap, then Emily Marks (?) in red sweater; Shap; Bonnie's back & Mollie on right.
    Reel 2. Sequence 13. Scene 2. New Orleans, LA: Visit of Ashley family to New Orleans: Mississippi River -- steamboat; on ferry: Bonnie in pony tails & Myrick in cowboy hat, then Daddy with hat on right; in front of Bonnie is Ann; Mother ? (has blue beret on); ? Blue cap with head down; Myrick in cowboy hat; shore scene -- boats, etc.; on same ferry?: Mother in white blouse with Ann & Bonnie in chairs in front of her; see Lykes Line ship.
    Reel 2. Sequence 13. Scene 3. New Orleans, LA: Visit cont'd at Audubon Zoo: Viewing apes: Daddy & Ann on right, then Myrick beyond Daddy; Bonnie (red hair) behind Ann & then beside her with back of Little Ann (brown shirt) on their right; Ann eating popcorn & Bonnie on her right. Front of elephants: Ann on left & Mollie (red pants) on right of screen; Ann on left & Bonnie on right. To zebras, hippopotamuses, camels, buffaloes. Riding pony -- Mollie; also riding -- Myrick; buffaloes in a line walking, then flamingoes, small porpoises in pool, alligators.
    Reel 2. Sequence 13. Scene 4. Location? woods or a park?: Miss Haber's (Floyd School) class - ? Ann or Bonnie's class.Ann in some close-ups of girls in class; eventually see Bonnie (red hair) next to someone in red, white & blue skirt (another redhead).
    Reel 2. Sequence 13. Scene 5. Location ? Easter egg baskets, then Shap (white shirt) with others in background.
    Reel 2. Sequence 14. Scene 1. Hull Street, front yard: Big Ann holding baby, probably Ann D. Stauss; Little Ann in short sleeved white blouse with Big Ann on right holding Ann D.; Uncle Eddie walking beside Mollie walking on low bMyrick wall.
    Reel 2. Sequence 14. Scene 2. Location? Lake ?: Close-up of empty skiff & adjacent one with Daddy (blue & white checkered shirt) & Myrick beside him; 2 others about Myrick's age & then male adult guiding small motorboat.
    Reel 2. Sequence 14. Scene 3. Bankhead Avenue, back yard: Bonnie in yellow shorts with ? Beside her ?
    Reel 2. Sequence 14. Scene 4. Helena, AL: Camp Talahi: counselors & campers in swim suits; Bonnie (dark blue suit) on right; Maybe Gray Thames (yellow suit) -- blonde hair -- shorter of 2 in yellow; campers jumping off large blown-up raft; Bonnie diving. Woods? On left, Bonnie (brown shorts) on right
    Reel 2. Sequence 14. Scene 5. Location? Close-up of ?. On boat: ? In red life preserver, Myrick in blue life preserver, Daddy in blue & white hat. Pier. Sting ray (large with white spots). Boat. Myrick walking towards camera with Shap in background & ?. Seated: Mary Ellis Carrere & Ginny; Shap in shirt with red & blue stripes. Scene of houses on shore from boat. Daddy's back.
    Reel 2. Sequence 14. Scene 6. Destin, FL: Gulf, deep-sea fishing: dolphin being caught by Mary Ellis Carrere with close-up of Mary Ellis & then holding dolphin. Myrick in blue designed trunks. Mary Ellis, then Ann & Bonnie & behind them on right is Myrick. Shap in red designed trunks & Myrick in blue & Meri Wood in inner tube. On water's edge -- Meri in inner tube & back of Ann ? On right is Mary Ellis (tall) & then Ann. All above in water. Ginny in greenish suit on right, Mary Ellis on left & Meri Wood with back to camera. at some point scene moves from Gulf to Santa Rosa Sound.
    Reel 2. Sequence 15. Scene 1. Mary Esther or Destin FL: Back of boat "MeriWood"; Destin: fishing boats; top of Meriwood; Mary Ellis Carrere -- Ann -- Ginny -- Bonnie; Meri Wood (red & white striped suit) & Shap; Uncle Phil with cigar; Daddy on left & Myrick on right; Mother (yellow sleeveless shirt); dark glasses (?); fishing "official"? & Daddy on right.
    Reel 2. Sequence 15. Scene 2. Mary Esther, FL: sound side of Santa Rosa Island: Myrick swimming; Shap in water & pier in background; Myrick jumping in & swimming; diving board at end of pier.
    Reel 2. Sequence 15. Scene 3. Perdido, AL: The Point: Bonnie at head, then Ann, then ?; Bonnie diving & then Ann diving; female in red suit dives & then Myrick who jumps off board; Bonnie does cartwheel off board; Myrick at end of board -- jumps off backwards; Bonnie & Ann swimming; Shap in water -- swimming; female (in red suit) skiing.
    Reel 2. Sequence 15. Scene 4. Location? Shap in shorts & suspenders, holding hand of ? -- very DARK.
    Reel 2. Sequence 15. Scene 5. Montgomery Country Club: Ginny on diving board; Myrick climbing out of pool; Ann goes off high dive.
    Reel 2. Sequence 16. Scene 1. Bankhead Avenue, driveway: back of station wagon & green Plymouth; Ann on bicycle & Myrick & Tootsie on right; Myrick holding black puppy & Bonnie leaning on bike & then Shap next to Ginny holding a puppy; Bonnie riding bike; Puppies eating; Shap holding puppy; DARK; puppy in clothes basket (bed for puppies); Bonnie beside basket with puppy.
    Reel 2. Sequence 16. Scene 2. Location? Halloween costumes.
    Reel 2. Sequence 16. Scene 3. Location? Mollie in white smock over green dress; Bonnie in lavender/purple dress